+51986230926

SUMMARY

I am a Software and Systems graduate from the SISE Institute, with a comprehensive career of more than 5 years in the industry. Proficient in all facets of Systems delivery, professional journey has encompassed roles in both frontend backend development, culminating in my current position as a Specialist in mobile application development with Flutter. I am deeply motivated, consistently striving to enhance my skill set, eager to acquire knowledge, and resolutely new dedicated to achieving my goals, both in my personal and professional endeavors.

EDUCATION

2013 - 2018	Software and Systems Professional Career Instituto Superior SISE
2015 - 2017	Java & .NET Application Specialist Instituto Superior SISE
2016	Web Services in Java CIBERTEC

CERTIFICATES

2021	Web Development School (Road to code) PLATZI
2020	Advanced FLUTTER course PLATZI
2019	FLUTTER & DART UDEMY
2017	MOBILE DEVELOPMENT GMD



FABIAN GARCIA. RONALD N.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FROMSOLVERS 08/2021 - 03/2024

Tech lead / Flutter Developer

- Technical leader in the development of the R10 Score Application for iOS and Android.
 - o Clean arquitecture, Business Logic Components, CI/CD (github actions), In App Purchase, Push Notifications, Firebase Services, Local Storage, youtube player, webview.
- Scroble App Development for iOS and Android (Available for Luxembourg Belgium) - Social, creative and fashion shopping.
 - o Google maps, Websockets, signalr, appsflyer sdk, QR scan.

Travels and tourism WARZSUD 08/02/2021 - 31/05/2021

Flutter Developer - Freelancer

- Android & iOS App Taxi Will (Taxi Service in Satipo Peru)
- Google Maps, Push Notification, Cloud Functions (TypeScript), Firestore, authentication (FB, GOOGLE, APPLE), Camera.

MDP CONSULTING S.A.C 26/08/2019 - 31/01/2021

Mobile Application Programmer Analyst

- Estimation, architecture, design, development, publication and documentation of Multiplatform Applications.
- SODIMAC (retail) projects:
 - o Paperless: Benefits Management System
 - App Android, App Enterprise iOS, WebApp Flutter
 - o SodAsistente: Chatbot Assistant App
 - App Android, App iOS Flutter
 - WebHook NodeJS / NLP & Dialogflow

Servicio Técnico: In-person technical service app

App Android – Flutter

ADEXUS PERÚ 01/04/2018 a 23/08/2019

Systems Programmer Analyst - Full Stack .NET

- Attention to ERP-SGH Requirements (Payroll, HR) in the agile Scrum framework.
- Backend refactoring of the ERP-SGH
- System attention of the Tareo Digital Cappazo:
 - o Web and Services in .NET
 - Mobile App in Java for Android.
 - > IDE: Android Studio
 - > ARO: MVP
 - Libs: GreenDao, Retrofit, ButterKnife

GMD - Grupo Graña y Montero 01/08/2015 - 31/03/2018

Software programmer

- Design of user interfaces for the Legal Process Management System.
- Maintenance of the ERP-SGH (people management system) in production
- Analysis of ETL processes for the migration of labor data of workers from the Human Management System (ERP-SGH).
- Implementation and Maintenance of reports in SOL Reporting Services of the ERP-SGH & Legal Process Management System.

TEC-ONE Perú 01/09/2013 - 01/10/2014

Help Desk Specialist in Hardware and Software.





REPUBLICA DEL PERÚ

MINISTERIO DE EDUCACIÓN ***

A NOMBRE DE LA NACIÓN



La Directora General del Instituto de Educación Superior Tecnológico Privado Peruano de Sistemas "SISE"

Por cuanto Don (ña): RONALD NEMESIO FABIAN GARCIA
Ha cumplido satisfactoriamente con las normas y disposiciones reglamentarias vigentes, le otorga el título de:
PROFESIONAL TÉCNICO EN SOFTWARE Y SISTEMAS

POR TANTO:

Se expide el presente TÍTULO para que se le reconozca como tal

Dado en LIMA a los 25 dias del mes de MAYO del 2018

BIRECCIUM GENERAL SISE - SHEET

DIRECTORA GENERAL

(Sello, firme, post-firma) Mg. LORENA GAONA DURAND Código Registro Institucional

Nº 0120 - 2018